question_data = [
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The &quot;Gympie Stinger&quot; is the deadliest plant in the world.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                      "question": "Steel is an alloy of Iron and Carbon.", "correct_answer": "True",
                                      "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Like with the Neanderthals, Homo sapiens sapiens also interbred with the Denisovans.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Shrimp can swim backwards.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Scientists accidentally killed the once known world&#039;s oldest living creature, a mollusc, known to be aged as 507 years old.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In the periodic table, Potassium&#039;s symbol is the letter K.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Sugar contains fat.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Pneumonoultramicroscopicsilicovolcanoconiosis is a synonym for the disease known as silicosis.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Sound can travel through a vacuum.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The most frequent subconscious activity repeated by the human body is blinking.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]
